uh my song is the song of our people we
were uh once young and then Hudson's Bay
Company came and took all the Furs and
so it's the pain of the Canadian people
1 two 3
4 yeah turn that bad up a little bit
louder faster yeah well that's
better uh pardon sorry but was that the
song one two three
4 fast it's Murray my sober coach paron
but is the song of Canada just a drum
beat on a Casio Keyboard okay well
you're a just like my ex-wife so
let's do it then I hate to swear I'm not
going to swear but this crap is that
better is no
good is that is that tast your for you
thanks so much you move on to the next
round um my my songs are going to be
magic I've Loved magic since I was a boy
U and I will need need a volunteer to
pick a card oh looks like we got one
here so please uh this is a deck of
cards and you can see that all the cards
are different take any card the deck
anyone you'd like maybe do a little bit
of
contortion well I just need to pick a
card okay it's kind of mesh on it's
difficult yeah it might be easier just
take with your hands okay don't don't
show me okay I didn't show you but I
have it oh can you show us okay you see
what the card is you got that card trunk
okay here we go tell me when to stop
shuffling stop right
here what was your card it was the King
of Diamonds that's it crackers oh good
God oh
God
amazing can use you again you don't have
to do that cuz that kind of upstages me
you can take a car with your hands next
time okay thank you okay Tonto we come
to the end of the show it's time for you
to vote eh for Jean Lis text one for the
unfinished Canadian song of Doug Gary
text one1 for the hilarious comedy of
gram comedian you got to text one1 for
the crazy things of Amy Amnesia you Tex
one1 and then for the magic of magic
mate you got to text one1 everybody on
CH us your songs torono is a winner and
and the votes will prove that shortly
oops here we go here we go okay all
right here we go we got a winner here
and everyone's a
[Music]
winner
yeah yeah yeah